linkshade.com 2014-06-25

# LinkShade Directory - Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or submit a website or article to the directory. 

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

• To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

• To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

• To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

• To process transactions

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

• To send periodic emails

> The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can opt out of receiving our newsletter by clicking the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of the newsletter email. If you no longer wish to receive ANY emails relating to websites or articles that you have submitted to our directory, your submissions must be removed from our directory and your account closed. If you wish to remove your submissions and close your account, please send an email to admin@dc-studioweb.com. You must state clearly which website and article submission you want us to remove (or state that "ALL submissions are to be removed"). If you want your account closed you must state this clearly. Upon receiving your email we will immediately remove the submissions you specify and close your account. PLEASE NOTE: submissions that have been removed CANNOT be reactivated - they are deleted from the system. If you wish, you could register and re-submit, and then your submissions would go through the normal approval process again before they would become active. You also have the option to request that your submission(s) be set to "inactive" (for example, if you are working on a website and do not wish it to show up in the directory until the work is complete). Please email admin@dc-studioweb.com and let us know which submission(s) you wish to deactivate. We will set them to "inactive" until you send another email to request that they be reset to "active"..

 **How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders by contacting customer service.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

 **Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

 **Submission Guidelines Disclaimer**

The submission guidelines for this site clearly state the type of content that will not be approved for inclusion on this site. You can view that information by looking at the submission guidelines. All submissions are human-reviewed. However, we cannot and do not guarantee that content which fails to meet our submission guidelines will never show up on the site. It is not possible to review every page of every website submitted to the directory, nor can we control the changes to website content that may be made after they have been approved for this directory. If you come across any submissions that you consider to be in contravention of our submissions guidelines, please inform us by emailing the details to admin[AT]linkshade.com. We appreciate your assistance in maintaining a high standard for the content of this directory.

 **Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

 **Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [web site privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/).

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://www.linkshade.com/contact.php  
admin[AT]linkshade.com
